{
    "questionAnswer" : {
        "0" : {
            "Difficulty": 0,
            "Question": "\"What is a bit?\"",
            "Answer": "\"Any pair of opposites\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"The ball of a mouse\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"Cable\""
        },
        "1" : {
            "Difficulty": 0,
            "Question": "\"The brain of any computer system is the\"",
            "Answer": "\"CPU\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"Keyboard\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"Mouse\""
        },
        "2" : {
            "Difficulty": 0,
            "Question": "\"1 kilobyte is equal to\"",
            "Answer": "\"1000 bytes\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"1024 bytes\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"1064 bytes\""
        },
        "3" : {
            "Difficulty": 0,
            "Question": "\"What is the name for the worldwide network infrastructure that links millions of computers together from around the world to communicate through wires, cables and wireless connections?\"",
            "Answer": "\"Internet\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"Keyboard\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"Mouse\""
        },
        "4" : {
            "Difficulty": 1,
            "Question": "\"8 bits make up of how many bytes\"",
            "Answer": "\"1\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"100\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"1000\""
        },
        "5" : {
            "Difficulty": 0,
            "Question": "\"What is computer science?\"",
            "Answer": "\"Scientific approach to computation and its applications\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"Study of human behavior and their minds\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"Study of life\""
        },
        "6" : {
            "Difficulty": 0,
            "Question": "\"What an electronic device that calculates, manipulates, and stores information?\"",
            "Answer": "\"Computer\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"Ninja\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"Vehicle\""
        },
        "7" : {
            "Difficulty": 1,
            "Question": "\"What do you use to repeat segments of code?\"",
            "Answer": "\"Loops\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"Rings\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"Repeaters\""
        },
        "8" : {
            "Difficulty": 0,
            "Question": "\"What do strings represent?\"",
            "Answer": "\"Character sequences\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"Objects\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"Integers\""
        },
        "9" : {
            "Difficulty": 0,
            "Question": "\"What is the main program, like Window's and Mac OSX, called that runs other programs?\"",
            "Answer": "\"Operating Systems\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"Computers\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"Nouns\""
        },
        "10" : {
            "Difficulty": 0,
            "Question": "\"Java is considered a what?\"",
            "Answer": "\"Programming Language\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"Delicious Coffee\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"Operating System\""
        },
        "11" : {
            "Difficulty": 0,
            "Question": "\"A GPU's purpose is to:\"",
            "Answer": "\"Process Graphics\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"Go Fast\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"Save your Data\""
        },
        "12" : {
            "Difficulty": 0,
            "Question": "\"Computers physically send bits by\"",
            "Answer": "\"Electricity, light, and radio waves\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"Mail carriers and mail trucks\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"Morse code and semaphores\""
        },
        "13" : {
            "Difficulty": 0,
            "Question": "\"A set of rules and standards used to communicate between machines is:\"",
            "Answer": "\"Protocol\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"Library\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"Algorithm\""
        },
        "14" : {
            "Difficulty": 0,
            "Question": "\"A step by step process to solve a problem is called:\"",
            "Answer": "\"Algorithm\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"Ethernet\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"Protocol\""
        },
        "15" : {
            "Difficulty": 0,
            "Question": "\"How many devices are allowed to have the same IP address?\"",
            "Answer": "\"None\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"2\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"All devices\""
        },
        "16" : {
            "Difficulty": 0,
            "Question": "\"What is considered a number that uniquely identifies a device on the network?\"",
            "Answer": "\"IP Address\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"Ethernet\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"TEST\""
        },
        "17" : {
            "Difficulty": 0,
            "Question": "\"Traditionally, how many bits are used in an IP address (IPv4)?\"",
            "Answer": "\"32\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"25\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"50\""
        },
        "18" : {
            "Difficulty": 0,
            "Question": "\"How many bits does an IPv6 use for an IP address\"",
            "Answer": "\"128\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"150\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"200\""
        },
        "19" : {
            "Difficulty": 0,
            "Question": "\"What is the physical way of communicating data through the world wide web?\"",
            "Answer": "\"HTTP\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"HTML\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"CSS\""
        },
        "20" : {
            "Difficulty": 0,
            "Question": "\"What language describes web documents for web pages\"",
            "Answer": "\"HTML\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"HTTP\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"XML\""
        },
        "21" : {
            "Difficulty": 0,
            "Question": "\"What language helps style a web page\"",
            "Answer": "\"CSS\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"XML\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"HTTP\""
        },
        "22" : {
            "Difficulty": 0,
            "Question": "\"What is considered hardware?\"",
            "Answer": "\"Physical components of a computer\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"Internet\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"Bits\""
        },
        "23" : {
            "Difficulty": 0,
            "Question": "\"What is software?\"",
            "Answer": "\"Digital instructions run by a computer\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"A mouse\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"A keyboard\""
        },
        "24" : {
            "Difficulty": 0,
            "Question": "\"What is a piece of software that has a specific task?\"",
            "Answer": "\"Program\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"Hardware\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"Ethernet\""
        },
        "25" : {
            "Difficulty": 0,
            "Question": "\"What is a program for browsing web pages from the internet?\"",
            "Answer": "\"Web browser\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"Word processor\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"Instant messenger\""
        },
        "26" : {
            "Difficulty": 1,
            "Question": "\"What does the acronym HTML stand for?\"",
            "Answer": "\"HyperText Markup Language\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"HyperTrans Markdown Language\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"HyperText Modified Language\""
        },
        "27" : {
            "Difficulty": 1,
            "Question": "\"What does the acronym CSS stand for?\"",
            "Answer": "\"Cascading Style Sheets\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"Coding Style Sheets\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"Coding Syntax Styles\""
        },
        "28" : {
            "Difficulty": 2,
            "Question": "\"What does the acronym API stand for?\"",
            "Answer": "\"Application Programming Interface\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"Automatic Protocol Interface\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"Automatic Protection Idiom\""
        },
        "29" : {
            "Difficulty": 2,
            "Question": "\"Which of these is the lowest abstract level programming language?\"",
            "Answer": "\"Machine code\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"C++\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"Java\""
        },
        "30" : {
            "Difficulty": 2,
            "Question": "\"What does the concept of 'semantics' relate to?\"",
            "Answer": "\"Meaning and intention.\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"Being unsure of what to do.\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"Following the correct structural rules of language.\""
        },
        "31" : {
            "Difficulty": 1,
            "Question": "\"Which of these are a good example of a computing 'Server'?\"",
            "Answer": "\"The computer that stores and provides the information.\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"The computer that uses and consumes the information.\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"The computer that encrypts the information.\""
        },
        "32" : {
            "Difficulty": 0,
            "Question": "\"A single Personal-Computer can have multiple cores? (CPUS)\"",
            "Answer": "\"True\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"False\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"A PC can have multiple cores if and only if it has multiple screens.\""
        },
        "33" : {
            "Difficulty": 0,
            "Question": "\"Computer programming has it's roots in these disciplines--\"",
            "Answer": "\"Arithmetic, algebra, geometry, and maths\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"English and Foreign Language\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"History and Medicine\""
        },
        "34" : {
            "Difficulty": 0,
            "Question": "\"One of history's first programmers was a woman--\"",
            "Answer": "\"True and it was Ada Lovelace\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"True and it was Marie Curie\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"False\""
        },
        "35" : {
            "Difficulty": 1,
            "Question": "\"Computers are used in Western Society for everyday day activities\"",
            "Answer": "\"True\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"False\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"SemiTrue, Computers are only used for very math-intensive activities.\""
        },
        "36" : {
            "Difficulty": 2,
            "Question": "\"What term describes the concept of ubiquitous computing that appears everywhere in users' lives?\"",
            "Answer": "\"Pervasive computing\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"Desktop computing\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"Library computing\""
        },
        "37" : {
            "Difficulty": 0,
            "Question": "\"What common tool readily uses computing and programming?\"",
            "Answer": "\"Mobile-Smart Phones\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"Lawn-mowers\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"Ruler\""
        },
        "38" : {
            "Difficulty": 1,
            "Question": "\"Where is Silicon Valley located?\"",
            "Answer": "\"San Francisco Bay Area in Southern California.\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"Los Angeles in Southern California.\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"San Diego Area in Southern California.\""
        },
        "39" : {
            "Difficulty": 2,
            "Question": "\"Which of these are the top computing schools and universities?\"",
            "Answer": "\"Stanford, Carnegie Mellon University, MIT\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"Arizona State University, Michigan Tech, Cal-state Riverside\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"Columbia, Brown, NotreDame\""
        },
        "40" : {
            "Difficulty": 2,
            "Question": "\"You need to be wealthy to learn programming? \"",
            "Answer": "\"False\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"True, you need at least 5 benzes to start programming.\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"True, you need a +1000$ PC to learn programming.\""
        },
        "41" : {
            "Difficulty": 1,
            "Question": "\"When was Apple Inc. founded?\"",
            "Answer": "\" April 1, 1976.\"",
            "Wrong1": "\" March 27, 1986\"",
            "Wrong2": "\" Janurary 11, 2007\""
        },
        "42" : {
            "Difficulty": 0,
            "Question": "\"Google was founded while its' owners were still in--\"",
            "Answer": "\" Graduate School.\"",
            "Wrong1": "\" Diapers\"",
            "Wrong2": "\" Jail\""
        },
        "43" : {
            "Difficulty": 0,
            "Question": "\"Amazon.com Inc is based in? (Headquarters)\"",
            "Answer": "\"Seattle, Washington\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"San Francisco, California\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"Ann Arbor, Michigan\""
        },
        "44" : {
            "Difficulty": 0,
            "Question": "\"n 2015, Amazon surpassed _______ as the most valuable retailer in the United States by market capitalization\"",
            "Answer": "\"Walmart\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"Target\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"Chipotle\""
        },
        "45" : {
            "Difficulty": 1,
            "Question": "\"Apple Inc. was founded by these two entrepenuers--\"",
            "Answer": "\"Steve Jobs and Steve Wozniak\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"Steve Jobs and Bill Gates\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"Steve Jobs and Steve-O\""
        },
        "46" : {
            "Difficulty": 2,
            "Question": "\"What qualities do you need to become a quality programmer and computer scientist?\"",
            "Answer": "\"Curious, Hardworking, and interest in Problem-Solving\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"Nerdy, Glasses, and Proficient at Video Games\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"Math genius, rap god, and world-class typist\""
        },
        "47" : {
            "Difficulty": 2,
            "Question": "\"What is RAM?\"",
            "Answer": "\"Random Access Memory\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"Read Anywhere Memory\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"Random Anti Matter\""
        },
        "48" : {
            "Difficulty": 1,
            "Question": "\"What mega media company merged with AOL at the turn of the century?\"",
            "Answer": "\"Time Warner\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"Comcast\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"Fox Media\""
        },
        "49" : {
            "Difficulty": 2,
            "Question": "\"Name the famous computer scientist who worked to break Nazi codes at Bletchley Park during WWII.\"",
            "Answer": "\"Alan Turing\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"Steve Jobs\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"Bill Gates\""
        },
        "50" : {
            "Difficulty": 2,
            "Question": "\"You need to be wealthy to learn programming? \"",
            "Answer": "\"False\"",
            "Wrong1": "\"True, you need at least 5 benzes to start programming.\"",
            "Wrong2": "\"True, you need a +1000$ PC to learn programming.\""
        },
        "51" : {
            "Difficulty": 1,
            "Question": "\"What year was Google founded?\"",
            "Answer": "\" 1998.\"",
            "Wrong1": "\" 2001\"",
            "Wrong2": "\" 2008\""
        },
        "52" : {
            "Difficulty": 0,
            "Question": "\"What Apple portable debuted in a choice of two fruity color schemes, Blueberry or Tangerine?\"",
            "Answer": "\" The iBook.\"",
            "Wrong1": "\" The iPhone.\"",
            "Wrong2": "\" The iPad.\""
        }
    }
}